<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BMIapp</string>
    <string name="height">Height:</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight:</string>
    <string name="calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="result">Category based on the BMI result:</string>
    <string name="underweight_1_description">Calculate</string>
    <string name="nav_history_title">History</string>
    <string name="nav_settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="nav_author_title">Author</string>
    <string name="select_unit_hint">Select a unit</string>
    <string name="height_unit">Height unit:</string>
    <string name="weight_unit">Weight unit:</string>
    <string name="cat_1_name">Underweight (Severe thinness)</string>
    <string name="cat_1_upper_bound">16.0</string>
    <string name="cat_1_description">Individuals in this category have a BMI value indicating a
        severely low body weight, which may pose health risks. Adequate nutritional intake and
        medical attention may be necessary to address potential concerns related to under-nutrition.</string>
    <string name="cat_2_name">Underweight (Moderate thinness)</string>
    <string name="cat_2_upper_bound">16.9</string>
    <string name="cat_2_description">This category includes individuals with a BMI suggesting
        moderate thinness. While not as severe as the "Severe Thinness" category, attention to
        proper nutrition and overall health is still crucial to prevent further weight loss.</string>
    <string name="cat_3_name">Underweight (Mild thinness)</string>
    <string name="cat_3_upper_bound">18.4</string>
    <string name="cat_3_description">Individuals in this category have a BMI indicating mild thinness.
        While they may not be severely underweight, it is advisable to monitor their weight and take
        steps to ensure they maintain a healthy balance through proper diet and lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="cat_4_name">Normal range</string>
    <string name="cat_4_upper_bound">24.9</string>
    <string name="cat_4_description">This is the ideal range for BMI, indicating a healthy weight
        relative to height. Individuals falling within this category generally have a lower risk
        of health issues associated with weight extremes.</string>
    <string name="cat_5_name">Overweight (Pre-obese)</string>
    <string name="cat_5_upper_bound">29.9</string>
    <string name="cat_5_description">Individuals in this category have a BMI suggesting excess weight,
        but they are not yet classified as obese. It is advisable for individuals in this range to
        adopt lifestyle changes such as healthier eating habits and increased physical activity to
        prevent further weight gain.</string>
    <string name="cat_6_name">Obese (Class I)</string>
    <string name="cat_6_upper_bound">34.9</string>
    <string name="cat_6_description">This category indicates the first level of obesity. Individuals
        with a BMI in this range may face an increased risk of obesity-related health issues,
        and interventions such as diet modification and regular exercise are typically recommended.</string>
    <string name="cat_7_name">Obese (Class II)</string>
    <string name="cat_7_upper_bound">39.9</string>
    <string name="cat_7_description">This represents a higher level of obesity, indicating a more
        significant excess of body weight. Health risks associated with obesity become more pronounced
        in this category, and medical supervision is often necessary to address potential complications.</string>
    <string name="cat_8_name">Obese (Class III)</string>
    <string name="cat_8_upper_bound">unlimited</string>
    <string name="cat_8_description">This is the most severe level of obesity, indicating a substantial
        excess of body weight. Individuals in this category are at the highest risk of obesity-related
        health problems. Medical intervention, including lifestyle changes, dietary modifications,
        and possibly surgical options, may be considered to manage health risks associated with severe obesity.</string>
    <string name="nav_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="alert_warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="alert_question">Do you really want to delete all the stored data?</string>
    <string name="alert_negative_answer">No</string>
    <string name="alert_positive_answer">Yes</string>
    <string name="detail_category_header">Category name</string>
    <string name="detail_description_header">Category description</string>
    <string name="bmi_score_header">BMI score</string>
    <string name="author_name">Krzysztof Głowacz</string>
</resources>